Relax.
Drop your shoulders.
Release the tension in your body.
Just breathe.
Thank you
for sharing in this moment,
being in this space with me.
You and I
Are one in the same.
I hear your heart beat
Can you hear it too?
How was your day?
Is it just getting started?
Or has the sun already set?
Or does the day melt from one day to the next?
Never stopping, always moving.
Always
moving.
The future is
Uncertain
Dark greys appear over the blue sky
but don’t lose sight
of the horizon ahead.
One heart
And air that is shared
And a body that is searching
Searching
For an answer.
For something more.
You and I
Are one in the same.
Lines erased
Dismantle the lines, the walls,
the imaginary boundaries between us.
Breathe.
Do you see?
You and I
are one in the same.
Are one.