What does it feel like?
Tell me
What does it feel like to have the earth beneath you?
Imagine, a weight pushing down on you.
On your shoulders, and pressing you deep into the ground.
What is it like?
Is the ground hard?
Is it cold?
Imagine being in a vast garden.
You are walking, and wandering through an endless field.
Now, imagine that with each step you take,
you sink slowly into the earth.
Step, by step, by step
until you are waist-deep in the soil,
one plant among others.
A daisy grows nearby, its petal gently tickling your ear.
What is the smallest movement you can make with your body?
Can you move your toe or even your ear?
Can you move a single eye lash?
Be gentle, be slow.
Focus on the little movements in your body.
Now gradually accelerate the movement.
Let it affect other parts of your body.
If you move fast enough,
if you twist and turn, will you break away from the soil?
From the earth’s embrace?
Look past the horizon.
The earth has begun to harden
Dry air, dry skin, slowly cracking from the heat.
Where are you, in this moment in time and space?
Time passes in the blink of an eye
And this moment fades as soon as it happens.
But a memory shared, can last a little longer.
And I think...
I think I can…
remember.
Yes, I do.
How it felt to be outside, by the mountains.
The earth below me was rough, uneven.
The terrain was unpredictable but there was no doubt
The ground was solid.
A slight force pulling me down,
stopping me from wandering, floating off the earth.
And I could feel it, I did.
My head towards the sun,
the sweat trickling down, caressing my spine.
My legs, steady, and connected to the earth.
The energy from the sun, traveling through me to nourish the earth.
Grass between my toes.
I turned my head up and could see the sky come alive.
The stories of my ancestors written in the stars.
There was a time when it was all alive.
And maybe it will be once again.