Look around you
Yes, look around and tell me, what do you see?
Can you imagine if the walls around you
got further and further away?
Expanding your space
Giving you room to move
To breathe
Close your eyes
Can you tilt your head up?
Face the sky above
And feel the sun’s heat
A gentle warmth that first touches your nose
Then spreads to your cheeks.
Let your head relax
Let it sway gently.
Breathe.
When you're ready, open your eyes.
Take in your surroundings.
And as you do, let your shoulders,
your spine, feel the weight of your head.
This weight I feel in my body
Is one I’ve kept with me for so long.
I feel it in my chest,
a pressure that travels from my core to my limbs
Till the tips of my toes, my fingers feel numb.
A space once vast,
the walls become tighter until the once
endless space suddenly illuminates itself to be finite.
The embers grow, they travel and feed off my body
an embrace that soon becomes
Suffocating.
Treat this screen as a window
And this window as a light
And look around you to remember
Where you are.
Grab onto the real.
Count the objects closest to you
1, 2, 3, 4
Count the memories left around you, within you
Memories taste as sweet as candy canes
But the real, what exists now,
tastes burnt.
Charred is my space.
Burnt is my body.
My air I no longer trust.
Will you breathe with me?
Your breath,
is my salvation.
And I hope
This
Will create
a new
beginning.